Noah-Gabriel Winkler

Calle Maestro Caballero, 82 03009 Alicante, ALC (ES)

(+34) 640861608 w.noah.gabriel@gmail.com

About me

Computer Engineering student in final stages of studies with current work experience and strong problem-solving abilities. A professional who combines technical and academic development, focused on continuous skill growth while completing university studies.

Languages

German - Native
English - fully qualified (C1)
Spanish - fully qualified
Valencian - basic competence
French - elemental competence

Certifications and Diplomas

- Elastic Stack Certification Formadores IT 2022.
- Basics in VUE Certification 2022.
- Honorary Diploma for 1st year of high school/secondary education for involvement in extracurricular projects.
- Cambridge CAE (C1) Certificate.
- Thirteenth place in the National Cybersecurity Institute (INCIBE) competition 2015 and 2017.

Experience

Gestión Tributaria Territorial/Programmer

JAN 2019 - CURRENT, ALFAZ DEL PI

Software Architect specialized in .NET integration, responsible for implementing various technologies in enterprise architectures, performing technical analysis and reviews, leading small development teams to deliver robust solutions.

Private classes/German language teacher

JAN 2019 - MAY 2022, ALFAZ DEL PI

Supermarket Costa Blanca/Helping staff

SEPT 2018 - MAY 2022, ALFAZ DEL PI

Supermarket Costa Blanca/Cashier

AUG 2017 - SEPT 2017, ALFAZ DEL PI

Education

University of Alicante/Computer Engineering

SEPT 2020 - CURRENT, SAN VICENTE - ALICANTE (ES)

I.S. Lope de Vega/Baccalaureate

SEPT 2008 - JUN 2018, BENIDORM - ALICANTE (ES)

Albrecht-Dürer Schule/Primary Schools

AUG 2006- JUN 2008, MECKENBEUREN - BADEN WÜRTTEMBERG (DE)

Competencias

- .NET: Development of ApiRest solutions for interconnecting various technologies, development of Proxies and Satellites, and Identity/OpenId (JWT) authentication servers. Using dependency injection and various design patterns, as well as ORM.
- *Oracle PL/SQL*: Development of stored **procedure** and function **packages**, and use of **Oracle Advanced Queuing** for database **synchronization**.
- **Angular**: **Frontend** maintenance and development with Clarity based on **TypeScript**.
- *RabbitMQ*: Development of data **synchronization** systems between different environments.
- -Elastic Stack: Development of logging and indexing systems.
- -Other: IIS, Jenkins, Entity, VUE, GIT, Python, Racket, Swift, DB2, ASP.NET, TypeScript/JavaScript, jQuery, AWS, Azure, OAuth, Docker, C++...